Guide to the Anspach Travel Bureau Collection of Tourism Literature, 1936-2014 and undated RL.00045
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Europe, 1956-2007 and undated; 7; 60 boxes
  - Spain, 139
    - General--Tourist Office of SpainTravel Notes and news releases, 1985-2002 (Box EUR40)
    - General--Travel planning, 1993-2003 and undated (Box EUR40)
    - Destinations, 1984-2002 (Box EUR40)
    - Almeria, 1974-1979 and undated (Box EUR41)
    - Andalusia, 1985-2002 and undated (Box EUR41)
    - Balearic Islands (including MallorcaMajorca), 1960-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR41)
    - Barcelona, 1967-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR41)
    - Barcelona--Hotels, 1968-2003 and undated (Box EUR41)
    - Barcelona--Maps, 1983-2000 and undated (Box EUR41)
    - Canary/Baleraric/Madeira Islands, 1964-1972 and undated (Box EUR42)
    - Canary Islands, 1970-1999 and undated (Box EUR42)
    - Castilla y Leon, 1984-1993 and undated (Box EUR42)
    - Cordoba, 1980-2000 (Box EUR42)
    - Costa Brava, 1968-1987 and undated (Box EUR42)
    - Costa de la Luz, 1984-1994 (Box EUR42)
    - Costa del Sol, 1970-1999 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR42)
    - Costa del Sol--Malaga, 1964-1986; 2 folders (Box EUR42)
    - Costa del Sol--Marbella, 1966-2001 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR42)
    - Costa del Sol--Sotogrande, 1965-1971 and undated (Box EUR42)
    - Costa del Sol--Torremolinos, 1969-1975 and undated (Box EUR42)
    - Gaudi, 1968 and undated (Box EUR42)
    - Granada, 1974-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR43)
    - Jaen, 1982-1984 (Box EUR43)
    - Madrid, 1963-2005 and undated; 3 folders (Box EUR43)
    - Madrid--Hotels, 1970-1997 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR43)
    - Madrid--Maps, 1967-1999 and undated (Box EUR43)
    - Madrid--Museums and monuments, 1982-2001 (Box EUR43)
    - Santiago de Campostela, 1990-2005 (Box EUR43)
    - Sevilla/Seville, 1960-2003 and undated (Box EUR43)
    - Toledo, 1980-1998 (Box EUR44)
    - Valencia, 1978 and undated (Box EUR44)
  - Spain/Portugal, 140
    - General, 1980-1981 (Box EUR44)
  - Switzerland, 141
    - General, 1966-1979 and undated (Box EUR44)
    - General--Hotels, 1975-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR44)
    - General--Maps, 1985-1999 and undated (Box EUR44)
    - General--Sightseeing, 1990-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR44)
    - General--Tourist information, 1984-1999 and undated (Box EUR44)
    - General--Transportation and touring services, 1983-1986 and undated (Box EUR45)
    - Basel, 1982-1993 and undated (Box EUR45)
    - Basel--Hotels, 1974-1992 and undated (Box EUR45)
    - Berne, 1979-1990 and undated (Box EUR45)
    - Berne--Hotels, 1959-1988 and undated (Box EUR45)
    - Burgenstock and Davos, 1985-1991 and undated (Box EUR45)
    - Geneva, 1986-1995 and undated (Box EUR45)
    - Geneva--Excursions, 1976-1999 (Box EUR45)
    - Geneva--Hotels, 1984-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR45)
    - Geneva--Maps, 1986-1999 and undated (Box EUR45)
    - Geneva--Restaurant guide (Le Coup de Fourchette), 1995 (Box EUR46)
    - Grindelwald, 1969-1983 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR46)
    - Gstaad, 1981-2004 and undated (Box EUR46)
    - Interlaken/Victoria/Jungfrau, 1967-1991 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR46)
    - Interlaken--Hotels, 1980-1999 and undated (Box EUR46)
    - Klosters, undated (Box EUR46)
    - Lausanne, 1970-1999 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR46)
    - Lausanne--Hotels, 1988-2003 and undated (Box EUR46)
    - Locarno/Lugano, 1983-1992 and undated (Box EUR46)
    - Lucerne/Luzern, 1970 and undated (Box EUR47)
    - Lucerne/Luzern--Hotels, 1969-1999 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR47)
    - Montreux/Vevey, 1960-1970 and undated (Box EUR47)
    - Montreux/Vevey--Hotels, 1983-1999 and undated (Box EUR47)
    - St. Moritz, 1987-2004 and undated (Box EUR47)
    - Zermatt, 1992-1999 and undated (Box EUR47)
    - Zurich, 1977-1994 and undated (Box EUR47)
    - Zurich--Hotels, 1977-2002 and undated (Box EUR47)
    - Other Swiss towns, 1986-1989 and undated (Box EUR47)
  - Turkey, 142
    - General, 1982-2006 and undated (Box EUR48)
    - Cruise lines, undated (Box EUR48)
    - Istanbul hotels, 1990-1996 and undated (Box EUR48)
  - United Kingdom (see also Ireland), 143
    - Country houses and lodging, 1984-1997 and undated (Box EUR48)
    - General, 1977-1984 and undated (Box EUR48)
    - England--General, 1999 and undated (Box EUR48)
    - England--General--British Airways publications, 1983-2003 and undated (Box EUR48)
    - England--General--British Heritage (publication), 1984-1996 and undated (Box EUR48)
    - England--General--British Tourist Authority publications, 1981-2001; 2 folders (Box EUR49)
    - England--General--BritRail, 1970-2005 (Box EUR49)
    - England--General--Castles and treasure houses, 1981-1991 and undated (Box EUR49)
    - England--General--Chauffeur services, 1973-1997 and undated (Box EUR49)
    - England--General--Country houses A-G, 1988-2006 and undated (Box EUR49)
    - England--General--Country houses--Great Fosters, 2003-2005 and undated (Box EUR49)
    - England--General--Country houses H-Z, 1984-2006 and undated (Box EUR49)
    - England--General--Golf, 1987-1993 and undated (Box EUR49)
    - England--General--Hanbury Manor, 1991-1994 and undated (Box EUR50)
    - England--General--Hotels, 1974-1993 and undated (Box EUR50)
    - England--General--Hotels--Pride of Britain publications, 1986-2006 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR50)
    - England--General--Maps, 1967-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR50)
    - England--General--Stationery and miscellaneous, undated (Box EUR50)
    - England--General--The Guide magazine, 1998-2000 (Box EUR51)
    - England--General--Tours, undated (Box EUR51)
    - England--General--Travel guides, 1981-2003; 4 folders (Box EUR51)
    - England--Bath--Hotels, 1983-1996 (Box EUR51)
    - England--Bath--Priory Hotel, 1992 and undated (Box EUR52)
    - England--Bath--Royal Cresent Hotel, 1985 and undated (Box EUR52)
    - England--Central England, 1973-2000 and undated (Box EUR52)
    - England--Chester, 1987 and undated (Box EUR52)
    - England--Cliveden, 1987-1997 and undated (Box EUR52)
    - England--Cotswolds, 1980-2000 (Box EUR52)
    - England--Cotswolds--Cotswold House Hotel, undated (Box EUR52)
    - England--Cotswolds--Feathers Hotel, 1985-1994 and undated (Box EUR52)
    - England--Cotswolds--Hartwell House and Spa, 1990-1996 and undated (Box EUR52)
    - England--Cotswolds/WorcestershireLygon Arms, 1987-1989 and undated (Box EUR52)
    - England--Devon--Hotels, 1981-1982 and undated (Box EUR52)
    - England--East England, 1969-2000 and undated (Box EUR52)
    - England--Hampshire--Hotels, 1974-2005 and undated (Box EUR53)
    - England--Lake District/Lakeland, 1973-1990 (Box EUR53)
    - England--London--Apartments, 1992-2001 and undated (Box EUR53)
    - England--London--Hotel chains, 2004 and undated (Box EUR53)
    - England--London--Hotels--51 Buckingham Gate, undated (Box EUR53)
    - England--London--Hotels A-B, 1969-2004 and undated (Box EUR53)
    - England--London--Hotels--Athenaeum, 1994 and undated (Box EUR53)
    - England--London--Hotels C, 1963-2004 and undated (Box EUR53)
    - England--London--Hotels--Claridge, 1987-1989 and undated (Box EUR53)
    - England--London--Hotels--Connaught, 2003 and undated (Box EUR53)
    - England--London--Hotels D-E, 1991-2001 (Box EUR54)
    - England--London--Hotels--Dorchester, 1993-2000 and undated (Box EUR54)
    - England--London--Hotels F-G, 1967-2003 (Box EUR54)
    - England--London--Hotels--Goring, 1994-2004 and undated (Box EUR54)
    - England--London--Hotels H-M, 1965-2005 and undated; 3 folders (Box EUR54)
    - England--London--Hotels--Mandarin Oriental, 2001-2003 and undated (Box EUR55)
    - England--London--Hotels N-P, 1971-1986 and undated (Box EUR55)
    - England--London--Hotels--Number Sixteen, 1989-1990 and undated (Box EUR55)
    - England--London--Hotels R, 1968-2001 and undated (Box EUR55)
    - England--London--Hotels--Ritz, 1991 and undated (Box EUR55)
    - England--London--Hotels S-W, 1968-1996 (Box EUR55)
    - England--London--Hotels--Savoy, undated (Box EUR55)
    - England--London--Hotels--Stafford, 1992-2004 and undated (Box EUR55)
    - England--London--Hotels--Sterling, undated (Box EUR55)
    - England--London--Maps, 1970-2003 and undated (Box EUR55)
    - England--London--Shopping, 1993 and undated (Box EUR56)
    - England--London--Sightseeing, 1966-2001 and undated; 3 folders (Box EUR56)
    - England--North Country, 1969-2000 and undated (Box EUR56)
    - England--Oxford/Windsor/Woodstock, 1987-1996 and undated (Box EUR56)
    - England--Manoir Ecole de Cuisine, 2000-2001 (Box EUR56)
    - England--Southern England, 1970-2000 and undated; 3 folders (Box EUR56)
    - England--Southwest England, 1981-1991 and undated (Box EUR57)
    - England--Stapleford Park, 1988-1990 (Box EUR57)
    - England--Sussex, 1988-1989 and undated (Box EUR57)
    - England--York, 1985-1999 and undated (Box EUR57)
    - Scotland--General, 1974-1977 and undated (Box EUR57)
    - Scotland--General--Accommodation and Prestige Tours, 1998-2001 (Box EUR57)
    - Scotland--General--Connoisseur's Scotland tours, undated (Box EUR57)
    - Scotland--General--Scottish Quest (publication), 1987-1997 (Box EUR57)
    - Scotland--Golf, 1983-2003 (Box EUR58)
    - Scotland--Golf--Old Course Golf and Country Club, 1999 and undated (Box EUR58)
    - Scotland--Highlands, 1985-1993 (Box EUR58)
    - Scotland--Hotel directories, undated (Box EUR58)
    - Scotland--Hotels A-H, 1983-2005 (Box EUR58)
    - Scotland--Hotels--Edinburgh, 1985-1999 and undated (Box EUR58)
    - Scotland--Hotels--Gleneagles, 1978-1994 and undated (Box EUR58)
    - Scotland--Hotels I-Z, 1985-2006 and undated (Box EUR59)
    - Scotland--Hotels--Turnberry, 1993 and undated (Box EUR59)
    - Scotland--Maps and travel, 1988-1999 and undated (Box EUR59)
    - Scotland--Sightseeing, 1988-1999 and undated (Box EUR59)
    - Scotland--Trains, 1983-2000 and undated (Box EUR59)
    - Scotland--Trains--Royal Scotsman, 1997-2006 (Box EUR59)
    - Wales--Hotels, 1987-2003 and undated (Box EUR59)
    - Wales--Sightseeing, 1972-1994 and undated (Box EUR59)
    - Wales--Tours, 1983-1991 and undated (Box EUR60)
    - Wales--Vacation guides, 1969-2001 and undated (Box EUR60)
  - Yugoslavia (includes post-breakup Balkan countries), 144
    - General, 1969-1991 and undated; 3 folders (Box EUR60)
    - Croatia, 1970-2004 and undated (Box EUR60)
    - Croatia--Dubrovnik, 1962-1983 and undated (Box EUR60)
    - Montenegro, 1972-1983 and undated; 2 folders (Box EUR60)
    - Serbia, 1964-1970 and undated (Box EUR60)
    - Slovenia, undated (Box EUR60)
- Mexico, 1940s-2006 and undated; 8; 6 boxes
  - General Files, 145
    - Ecotourism/Sports/Adventure, undated (Box MEX1)
    - History/Archaeology brochures, 1980-1996 and undated (Box MEX1)
    - Hotels and resorts, 1970-2004 and undated (Box MEX1)
    - Maps and miscellaneous, 1967-1973 and undated; 2 folders (Box MEX1)
    - Regional/Topical brochures, 1986-1996 and undated (Box MEX1)
    - Travel planning, 1990-2005 (Box MEX1)
    - Villas and condominiums, 2001-2005 (Box MEX1)
    - Acapulco, 1966-2001 and undated; 3 folders (Box MEX2)
    - Baja, 1971-1998 and undated; 2 folders (Box MEX2)
    - Baja--Cabo San Lucas, 1998-2005 and undated (Box MEX2)
    - Baja--Los Cabos, 1996-2006 and undated; 2 folders (Box MEX2)
    - Cancun, 1975-2002 and undated; 3 folders (Box MEX3)
    - Chihuahua, 1940s-1960s (Box MEX3)
    - Ciudad Valles, 1950s (Box MEX3)
    - Colima, 2001 and undated (Box MEX3)
    - Copper Canyon, 1960s-1998 (Box MEX3)
    - Costa Careyes, 1999 and undated (Box MEX3)
    - Cozumel, 1975-1995 and undated (Box MEX4)
    - Cuernavaca, 1950s-1981 (Box MEX4)
    - Guadalajara, 1967-1989 and undated; 2 folders (Box MEX4)
    - Huatulco, 2001 and undated (Box MEX4)
    - Isla Mujeres, 1970-1989 and undated (Box MEX4)
    - Isla Navidad, 1998 (Box MEX4)
    - Ixtapa/Zihuatanejo, 1970s-2004 and undated; 3 folders (Box MEX4)
    - Juanajuato, 1990s (Box MEX4)
    - Juarez, 1973 (Box MEX4)
    - Manzanillo, 1981-1999 and undated; 2 folders (Box MEX4)
    - Mazatlan, 1969-1993 and undated; 2 folders (Box MEX4)
    - Merida, 1967-1991 and undated (Box MEX4)
    - Mexican Caribbean/Quintana Roo, 2003 and undated (Box MEX5)
    - Mexico City, 1964-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box MEX5)
    - Michoacan, 1966 and undated (Box MEX5)
    - Michoacan--Morelia, 1999 (Box MEX5)
    - Monterrey, 1973-1992 and undated (Box MEX5)
    - Morelos, 1979 and undated; 2 folders (Box MEX5)
    - Nogales, 1950s (Box MEX5)
    - Oaxaca, 1970-1999 and undated (Box MEX5)
    - Playa del Carmen, undated (Box MEX5)
    - Puebla, 1962-1990s and undated (Box MEX5)
    - Puerto Vallarta, 1969-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box MEX5)
    - Punta Mita, 2000 and undated (Box MEX5)
    - Queretaro, 1986 and undated (Box MEX6)
    - Quintana Roo (includes information on CozumelIsla Mujeres), 1969-1975 and undated (Box MEX6)
    - Riviera Maya, 2001-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box MEX6)
    - San Cristobal, 1993 and undated (Box MEX6)
    - San Miguel de Allende, 1970s-2001 and undated (Box MEX6)
    - Taxco, 1940s-1988 and undated (Box MEX6)
    - Valle de Bravo, undated (Box MEX6)
    - Veracruz, 1973-1988 and undated (Box MEX6)
    - Yucatan, 1967-2004 and undated; 3 folders (Box MEX6)
- Pacific Region, 1960-2006 and undated; 9; 9 boxes
  - General, 146
    - Air New Zealand/ATS Tours, 2004-2006 (Box PAC1)
    - Island Destinations/Southern Crossings, 2002-2004 (Box PAC1)
    - Miscellaneous brochures, 1969-1982 and undated (Box PAC1)
    - Miscellaneous island reports, undated (Box PAC1)
    - Qantas/Jetabout, 2004-2006 (Box PAC1)
    - Tourism Council of the South Pacifictravel manual, 1992 (Box PAC1)
    - Travel packages, 1997-2005 (Box PAC1)
  - Antarctica, 147
    - General, 1984-2006 (Box PAC1)
  - Australia, 148
    - General, 1964-1998 and undated; 3 folders (Box PAC2)
    - Maps, 1988 and undated (Box PAC2)
    - Rail lines, 1995-1998 and undated (Box PAC2)
    - Sights and lodging, 1964-1973 and undated (Box PAC2)
    - Tour guides, 1987-2005 and undated (Box PAC2)
    - Youth programs (18-35), 1987 (Box PAC2)
    - Capital Territory--Canberra, undated (Box PAC2)
    - New South Wales, 2004 and undated (Box PAC2)
    - New South Wales--Sydney, 1985-2004 and undated (Box PAC2)
    - New South Wales--Sydney--Hotels, 1993-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box PAC3)
    - Outback/Northern Territory, 1987 and undated (Box PAC3)
    - Queensland--Brisbane, 1986-1997 and undated; 2 folders (Box PAC3)
    - Queensland--Great Barrier Reef, 1980-2004 and undated; 3 folders (Box PAC3)
    - Queensland--Port Douglas/Cairns, 1988-1996 and undated (Box PAC3)
    - South Australia--Adelaide, 1986-1987 and undated (Box PAC3)
    - Tasmania--Hobart, 1987-1989 and undated (Box PAC3)
    - Victoria, 1980-1987 and undated; 2 folders (Box PAC4)
    - Victoria--Melbourne, 1985-1999 and undated (Box PAC4)
    - Western Australia--Perth, 1988 and undated (Box PAC4)
  - Australia/New Zealand, 149
    - Tour packages, 1995-2006 and undated; 3 folders (Box PAC4)
  - Cook Islands (including Barotongo), 150
    - General, 1977-2001 and undated (Box PAC4)
  - Tahiti, 160
    - General (includes information on Bora Bora), 1964-2003 and undated; 3 folders (Box PAC8)
    - Honeymoon/Weddings, 2002-2006 (Box PAC8)
    - Hotels, 1975-2003 and undated (Box PAC8)
    - Tahiti Tourisme, 2004 and undated (Box PAC8)
    - Tahiti Tourist and Development Board, 1982 (Box PAC8)
    - Tour packages, 2002-2006 and undated (Box PAC8)
    - Tour packages--Brendan, 2001-2005 (Box PAC9)
    - Bora Bora, 1987-2003 and undated (Box PAC9)
    - Huahine, 1987-1993 (Box PAC9)
    - Moorea, 1987-1993 and undated (Box PAC9)
  - Fiji, 151
    - General, 1964-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box PAC5)
    - Cruises and transportation, 1984-1987 and undated (Box PAC5)
    - Hotels, 1984-2001 and undated (Box PAC5)
    - Hotels--Regent, 1993 (Box PAC5)
    - Hotels--Turtle Island, 1985-2002 (Box PAC5)
    - Hotels--Wakaya Club, 2002 (Box PAC5)
    - Tours--Brendan/TAPA, 1985-2005 (Box PAC5)
    - Tours--Jetabout/Islands in the Sun, 2001-2004 (Box PAC5)
    - Tours--Miscellaneous packages, 1985-2003 and undated (Box PAC5)
  - Guam/Micronesia, 152
    - General, 1970-2000 and undated (Box PAC5)
  - Marquesas, 153
    - General, 1990-2002 (Box PAC5)
  - New Caledonia, 154
    - General, 1983 (Box PAC5)
  - New Zealand, 155
    - General, 1960-1973 and undated (Box PAC6)
    - Destinations, 1984-2001 and undated (Box PAC6)
    - Ecotourism/Adventure, 1981-2002 and undated (Box PAC6)
    - Farm Holidays, 1987-2004 and undated (Box PAC6)
    - Hotels, 1991-2002 and undated (Box PAC6)
    - Hotels--Huka Lodge, 1992-2005 and undated (Box PAC6)
    - Maps, 1973-1988 and undated (Box PAC6)
    - Tour guides, 2003-2006 (Box PAC6)
    - Tourist information, 1983-2003 and undated (Box PAC6)
    - Transportation, 1984-2001 and undated (Box PAC6)
    - Travel planning, 1983-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box PAC6)
    - Auckland, 1984-2001 and undated (Box PAC6)
    - Christchurch/Lyttleton, 1984-1987 and undated (Box PAC7)
    - Dunedin/Otego, 1995-2001 and undated (Box PAC7)
    - Napier, 1987-2001 and undated (Box PAC7)
    - Queenstown/Milford, 1982-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box PAC7)
    - Rotorua, 1987-1999 and undated (Box PAC7)
    - South Island/Picton, undated (Box PAC7)
    - Wellington, 1999-2000 and undated (Box PAC7)
  - Norfolk Island/Melanesia, 156
    - General, undated (Box PAC7)
  - Papua New Guinea, 157
    - General (includes informaton on Melanesia), 1971-1987 and undated; 3 folders (Box PAC7)
  - Samoa, 158
    - General, 1966-1998 and undated (Box PAC7)
  - South Pacific Islands, 159
    - General (includes LaulasiNew HebridesSolomon IslandsRabdulMicronesia), 1969-1972 and undated (Box PAC7)
  - Tonga, 161
    - General, 1984 and undated (Box PAC9)
- South America, 1957-2006 and undated; 10; 3 boxes
  - General, 162
    - Abercrombie & Kent, 2005-2006 and undated (Box SAM1)
    - Maps, 1959-1966 (Box SAM1)
    - Miscellaneous brochures, 1968-2004 (Box SAM1)
    - Tours, 1966-1981 and undated (Box SAM1)
  - Antarctica/Falklands, 163
    - General, undated (Box SAM1)
  - Argentina, 164
    - General, 1960-1992 and undated; 2 folders (Box SAM1)
    - Hotels, 1970-2004 and undated (Box SAM1)
  - Bolivia, 165
    - General, 1971-1993 (Box SAM1)
  - Brazil, 166
    - General, 1950s-2002 and undated; 2 folders (Box SAM1)
    - Hotels, 1982-1996 and undated (Box SAM1)
    - Rio de Janeiro, 1971-1991 and undated (Box SAM2)
    - Rio de Janeiro--Hotels, 1981-1992 and undated (Box SAM2)
  - British Guiana, 167
    - General, 1958-1974 and undated (Box SAM2)
  - Chile, 168
    - General, 1957-2004 and undated; 2 folders (Box SAM2)
    - Hotels, 1958-2004 and undated (Box SAM2)
    - Patagonia/Antarctica, 1986-2003 (Box SAM2)
    - Santiago, 1999 and undated (Box SAM2)
    - Sports/Adventure, 1983 and undated (Box SAM2)
  - Colombia, 169
    - General, 1966-1983 and undated; 2 folders (Box SAM2)
  - Easter Island, 170
    - General, 1974-1981; 2 folders (Box SAM2)
  - Ecuador, 171
    - General, 1967-2006 and undated; 2 folders (Box SAM2)
    - Galapagos Islands, 1969-1995 and undated (Box SAM2)
    - Galapagos Islands, 1968-1984 and undated (Box SAM3)
    - Hotels, 1968-1996 and undated (Box SAM3)
    - Metropolitan Touring brochures, 1981-1990s (Box SAM3)
  - Paraguay, 172
    - General, undated (Box SAM3)
  - Peru, 173
    - General, 1957-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box SAM3)
    - Amazon, 1966-1989 (Box SAM3)
    - Hotels, 1969-1999 and undated (Box SAM3)
  - Surinam, 174
    - General, 1969-1973 and undated (Box SAM3)
  - Venezuela, 176
    - General, 1969-1992 and undated (Box SAM3)
    - Hotels, 1980-1991 and undated (Box SAM3)
  - Uruguay, 175
    - General, 1950s-2001 and undated (Box SAM3)
  - South and Central America, 177
    - Brochures, 1979-2006 (Box SAM3)
- United States, 1936-2014 and undated; 11; 52 boxes
  - General, 178
    - Airline routes, 1964-1966 (Box USA1)
    - Bed & Breakfast directory, undated (Box USA1)
    - Maps--Continental U.S., 1960-1976 and undated (Box USA1)
    - Maps--Eastern U.S., 1975-1983 (Box USA1)
    - Maps--Hertz Dist-O-Map, undated (Box USA1)
    - Maps--Historical/Cultural, 1953-1977 and undated (Box USA1)
    - Maps--Midwest and Central U.S., 1953-1983 (Box USA1)
    - Maps--Northeast U.S., 1960-1984 (Box USA1)
    - Maps--Southern U.S., 1974-1976 (Box USA1)
    - Maps--Western U.S., 1960-1983 (Box USA1)
    - Parks, 1948-2001 and undated (Box USA2)
    - Ranches--General, 1981-2004 and undated (Box USA2)
    - Ranches--Arizona, 1981-2002 and undated (Box USA2)
    - Ranches--British Columbia (Canada), 2000-2001 (Box USA2)
    - Ranches--California, 1978-1991 and undated (Box USA2)
    - Ranches--Colorado, 1980-2003 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA2)
    - Ranches--Idaho, undated (Box USA2)
    - Ranches--Michigan, undated (Box USA2)
    - Ranches--Montana, 1996-2005 and undated (Box USA3)
    - Ranches--Texas, 1986-1995 and undated (Box USA3)
    - Ranches--Utah [Includes Robert Redford Sundance Farms], 1999 and undated (Box USA3)
    - Ranches--Wyoming, 2002-2003 and undated (Box USA3)
    - Ranchesmiscellaneous notes, 2005 (Box USA3)
  - Alabama, 179
    - General, 1950s-1990 and undated (Box USA3)
  - Alaska, 180
    - General, 1957-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA3)
    - Anchorage, 1986-2004 and undated (Box USA3)
    - Cruises/Ferries, 1992-2004 and undated (Box USA3)
    - Denali, 1989-2006 and undated (Box USA4)
    - Fishing, 1992-1993 and undated (Box USA4)
    - Glacier Bay, 1991 and undated (Box USA4)
    - Helicopter/Air tours, 1991-1995 and undated (Box USA4)
    - Hotels, 1970s-2003 and undated (Box USA4)
    - Juneau/Sitka, 1972-1992 and undated (Box USA4)
    - Kenai, 1992-2005 and undated (Box USA4)
    - Ketchikan, 1987-2004 and undated (Box USA4)
    - Maps, 1936-2005 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA4)
    - Parks, 1985 and undated (Box USA4)
    - Rail, 1992-2005 and undated (Box USA4)
    - Tour packages, 1990-2005 (Box USA4)
    - Transportation, 1993-1999 and undated (Box USA4)
    - Travel/Vacation planning, 1981-2003 and undated (Box USA4)
    - Wilderness/Adventure, 1984-2005 and undated (Box USA5)
  - Arizona, 181
    - General, 1991-2005 (Box USA5)
    - General--Attractions, 1984-2003 and undated (Box USA5)
    - General--Hotels/Resorts, 1978-2003 and undated (Box USA5)
    - General--Parks, 1950s-1994 and undated (Box USA5)
    - Carefree, 1985-1989 and undated (Box USA5)
    - Grand Canyon, 1978-2000 and undated; 2 folders (Box USA5)
    - Mesa, 1991-1993 and undated (Box USA5)
    - Phoenix--General, 1991-2006 (Box USA5)
    - Phoenix--Hotels--General, 1987-1993 and undated (Box USA6)
    - Phoenix--Hotels--Biltmore, 1981-2000 and undated (Box USA6)
    - Phoenix--Hotels--Hilton, 1994-1999 and undated (Box USA6)
    - Phoenix--Hotels--Royal Palms, 1997 and undated (Box USA6)
    - Scottsdale--General, 1993-2004 and undated (Box USA6)
    - Scottsdale--Hotels--General, 1993-2001 and undated (Box USA6)
    - Scottsdale--Hotels--Camelview, undated (Box USA6)
    - Scottsdale--Hotels--Hyatt, 1998-2004 and undated (Box USA6)
    - Scottsdale--Hotels--Phoenician, 1992-2004 (Box USA6)
    - Scottsdale--Hotels--Resort Suites, 1992-2002 and undated (Box USA6)
    - Scottsdale--Hotels--Scottsdale Plaza, undated (Box USA6)
    - Sedona--General, 2000 and undated (Box USA6)
    - Sedona--Hotels, 1984-2003 and undated (Box USA7)
    - Tempe, 1991-1993 and undated (Box USA7)
    - Tucson--General, 1970s-2004 and undated (Box USA7)
    - Tucson--Canyon Ranch Spa, 1995-2004 (Box USA7)
    - Tucson Planner, 1998 (Box USA7)
    - Tucson--Ranches, 1985-2005 and undated (Box USA7)
    - Wigwam, 1992-2006 and undated (Box USA7)
  - Arkansas, 182